

CONTACT

- andres.orozco.dev@gmail.com
- (+1) 631-459-8183
- Miami, Fl
- Work authorization in USA | COL
- Github
- LinkedIn

ABOUT ME

Frontend developer with two years of experience, with good practices in layout and building highly adaptable sites, I am an enormously curious person in learning functionalities with modern libraries and frameworks. I like to work in a team and to learn something new every day.

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate

Andres F. Orozco

Systems Engineer | Frontend Developer | Python Developer

WORK HISTORY

Middle Software Developer (Sistecredito S.A.S.)

Decembre 2021 - March 2022 (Medellin, Col)

• Building and maintaining web applications in Angular.

Junior Software Developer (Sistecredito S.A.S.)

July 2020 - November 2021 (Medellin, Col)

• Building and maintaining web applications in Angular.

Apprentice of Systems engineering (Multimedia Lab.)

January 2020 - July 2020 (Medellin, Col)

 Building and maintaining web applications in Angular - React -React Native - Wordpress.

EDUCATION

2021 Bachelor's Degree in Systems Engineering
Universidad de Medellin.

2014 Degree High School

Instituto San Carlos de la salle.

SKILLS

